I'm getting tired of people telling me
that AI tooling only works for demos and
prototypes. I'm tired of hearing that AI
doesn't work for legacy applications.
We use Claude Flow and Claude Code all
the time for legacy code bases. We also
use it for architectural work, not just
coding. I'm Derek Ashmore from Asperitis
Consulting and I help companies through
app modernization projects and cloud
hosting projects all the time. I want to
take you through how we use Cloudflow
dayto-day um and particularly with uh
app modernization. I'm speaking and
doing a workshop at AI Native DevCon on
this very topic. Registration can be had
at a native.iodevcon.
That is a native.io/devcon.
I'd love to see you there.